vizualize.me 2019-11-06

# Privacy Policy - Vizualize.me Help Center

## Your privacy is important to us

This policy regarding our privacy practices (the "Privacy Policy") describes how we collect and use your personal data when you visit and use the services of our website available at:  [http://vizualize.me](http://vizualize.me/) ("Website"). When you sign-up and use our Website and services, you are consenting to the processing of your personal data. "Personal data" means information relating to you or another identified or identifiable natural person.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not govern what our Website users do on their own blogs and we are not responsible for the information collection and use practices of their individual blogs and bloggers.

If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our services or provide Vizualize.me with your personal data.

## Information we collect

  * E-mail address and password when you sign-up for an account.
  * Education information
  * Job history - title, company name, location and employment dates
  * Job skills, languages, awards, recommendations and similar
  * Any other personal information you enter into your profile
  * Links to your personal profiles (Twitter, Linkedin, Facebook)
  * When you access our services online, our web servers automatically create records of your visit. These records typically include IP-address, access times, the sites linked from, pages visited, the links and features used, the content viewed or requested, browser or application type, and other such information. See also our Information on Cookies usage below.

## How we use your personal data

We may process your personal data for the following purposes. One or more purposes may apply simultaneously. 

  * We use your personal data to help you efficiently access your information after you log-in and provide personalized content and information to you.
  * We may use your personal data to develop and manage our Website, services, customer care, sales and marketing.
  * We may use your personal data to communicate with you, for example to inform you that our services have changed or to send you critical alerts and other such notices relating to our services and to contact you for customer care related purposes.
  * All Vizualize.me profiles are publicly accessible via our Website by default. When you create or reconfigure a Vizualize.me profile, your profile may be listed publicly on our Services, including on a directory page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing lists, do not require registration.
  * If you wish to make your profile private, you can un-publish your profile or delete your account.

## Sharing of your personal data

Vizualize.me does not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose your personal data to third parties unless otherwise stated below. 

  * If you publish your profile publicly, your profile will be listed publicly on our Services, including on a directory page and in search results. Your personal data may become searchable on search engines such as Google, Bing and Yahoo. 
  * We may share your personal data if we have your consent to do so.
  * You may access third party services through the using of our services, for example by clicking on externally-pointing links. You may also choose to share the profile that you have created in our Website, with those third party services (for example, by sharing your profile to Twitter or Facebook). This Privacy Policy only governs information we collect and you are responsible for reading and understanding those third party services’ privacy policies.
  * We may be obligated by mandatory law to disclose your personal data to certain authorities or other third parties, for example, to law enforcement agencies in the countries where we operate. We may also disclose and otherwise process your personal data in accordance with applicable law to defend Vizualize.me legitimate interests, for example, in civil or criminal legal proceedings.
  * If we decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize our businesses in certain countries, this may involve us disclosing personal data to prospective or actual purchasers and their advisers, or receiving personal data from sellers and their advisers. By using this site, you acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Vizualize.me may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## The privacy of children

Vizualize.me services are intended for general audiences. Vizualize.me does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without the consent of their parents or guardians. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. 

## The quality of personal data

We take reasonable steps to keep the personal data we possess accurate and to delete incorrect or unnecessary personal data. 

We encourage you to access your personal data through your account from time to time to ensure that it is up to date. 

## Information on Cookies usage

Cookies are pieces of text that may be sent to and saved by your web browser when you access our Website; your web browser stores these cookies in a way associated with each website you visit, and you can see your cookies through your browser settings. 

We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you use our services. Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain information that personally identifies you, and we don’t combine the general information collected through cookies with other such information to tell us who you are. However, we do use cookies to identify that you have logged in and that your web browser has accessed aspects of the services, and we may associate that information with your account if you have one. This information, in turn, is sometimes used to personalize your experiences on the services. 

Most web browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your web browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. Please note that this Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. 

## What are your rights?

  * You have a right to know what personal data we have about you. 
  * You have a right to have incomplete, incorrect, unnecessary or outdated personal data deleted or updated. 
  * You have the right to be forgotten
  * You have a right to request that we stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes or on other compelling legal grounds.
  * You have the right to request that your data be exported
  * You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time

Please refer to our  [Help](https://vizme.helpscoutdocs.com/) center to read about how to update or delete your personal data. 

## How we store your data

Because the Internet is not a 100% secure environment we cannot guarantee the security of personally identifiable information. Please remember that: 

  * You provide personal data at your own risk. Unfortunately, there is some risk that an unauthorized third party may find a way to circumvent our security systems or that transmission of your information over the Internet will be intercepted.
  * You are responsible of your username and password: keep them secret and safe!
  * If you believe your privacy has been breached, please contact us immediately on [vizualize.me@gmail.com](mailto:vizualize.me@gmail.com)

## How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at   [vizualize.me@gmail.com](mailto:vizualize.me@gmail.com)

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Vizualize.me may modify or update this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it periodically. Your continued use of this site or Vizualize.me services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of these changes.

__

Still need help? Contact Us Contact Us

Last updated on May 18, 2018
